firstpalette.com 2017-07-13

# Privacy Policy | FirstPalette.com

The privacy of our visitors to FirstPalette.com is important to us. 

At FirstPalette.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit FirstPalette.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use third party advertisements on FirstPalette.com to support our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you: 

We may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads "Google Privacy Policy").
